homebiz-direct.com 2013-08-06

# Privacy Policy

**Website Privacy Policy**

By using this Website, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes will be posted on this page and visitors are encouraged to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

**Information Collected Automatically**

In some cases, we may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical information when you connect to our Website that is not personally identifiable information. Examples of this type of information include the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. Also, when you view our Website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Website to better match your interests and preferences. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

**Privacy Information for Persons 13 Years and Older**

We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address) through our Website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you. For example, if you choose to sign up for a newsletter, we will request your name and email address. 

When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: 

We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; 

We employ other companies to perform certain functions on our behalf, such as processing orders and delivering packages, conducting surveys and sending you mailings regarding our products and these companies have access to your personal information and; 

We may contact you regarding promotions and other offers regarding our products that may interest you. We do not now, and do not intend to, sell, rent or market personally identifiable information about you to third parties. We share information only with subsidiaries of this site and may use it to send you promotions and product information. 

**Children Under 13**

Our Privacy Policy applies to children as well as adults. There are some extra precautions that we take, however, with respect to collecting information from children under 13. 

We encourage parents and guardians to explore our Website with their children. 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from your children under 13 on-line without first obtaining permission from the child’s parent or guardian. 

Our Website does not offer activities that allow your child disclose your child’s personal information publicly (for example through chat rooms or message boards). 

We do not share your child’s personally identifiable information with third parties. Please also note that we do not offer activities that require the ongoing collection and use of personally identifiable information provided by children. 

**Use of Website and Website Material**

This Website is provided for your personal noncommercial use. You may not copy material from this Website for commercial use. You may copy material in limited quantities from this Website for your personal noncommercial use provided that our copyright notice is affixed to the copied material. We reserve the right to terminate, at any time, your permission to make personal copies of material from this Website. 

You are prohibited from using this Website to post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, profane material, any material that infringes on any copyright, trademark or other proprietary right or any material that could constitute or encourage unlawful conduct. We may, from time to time, monitor or review material transmitted or posted using this Website and reserve the right to delete any material we deem inappropriate. This Website is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from any material transmitted or posted using this Website. 

**Ownership of Intellectual Property**

All material on this website is copyrighted, either by us or third party providers. Notwithstanding any other term or condition in this agreement, We retains ownership to the copyright in this Website and all material from this Website unless otherwise indicated. 

**Severed Provisions and Entire Agreement**

If any provision of this agreement is unenforceable, that provision shall be deemed severed from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. 

This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the subject matter. 

We may modify these Terms of Use at any time and without notice. You are bound by any modifications and should therefore periodically visit this page to review Terms of Use to which you are bound.
